Class of 1920 Records, 1916-1965
Smith College Archives
Class of 1920 Records
1916-1965
Smith College. Class of 1920.
RG 80 UUID:2acd26bd-3d89-4c5f-b279-60f45f6eaf3b
18 boxes (14.17 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 18 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1920.
The Class of 1920 was the forty-second graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1920 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1920, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1920 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 1)
- Commencement Music 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 2)
- Commencement Photographs 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 3)
- Freshman Frolic 1916 (Box 1928, Folder 4)
- Freshman Handbook 1916-1917 (Box 1928, Folder 5)
- Groups 1916-1920 (Box 1928, Folder 6)
- Hoop Rolling 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 7)
- Junior Prom 1919 (Box 1928, Folder 8)
- Junior Ushers 1919 (Box 1928, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 11)
- Last Sing 1920 (Box 1928, Folder 12)
- Class Letters 1949-1976 (Box 1928, Folder 13)
- Memorials 1935-1960 (Box 1928, Folder 14)
- Organization 1916 (Box 1928, Folder 15)
- Reunions undated (Box 1928, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1923-1925 (Box 1928, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1930 (Box 1928, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1935 (Box 1928, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1940-1945 (Box 1928, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1950-1955 (Box 1928, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1960-1965 (Box 1928, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1970-1975 (Box 1929, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1980-1985 (Box 1929, Folder 2)
- Reunions Songs undated (Box 1929, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics 1920 (Box 1929, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1920 (Box 1929, Folder 5)
- Sophomore Reception 1918 (Box 1929, Folder 6)
- Step Sings 1920 (Box 1929, Folder 7)
- Songs undated (Box 1929, Folder 8)
- Class Supper 1920 (Box 1929, Folder 9)
- Class Secretary's Records (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Records (Box OV)
- Reunion Memorabilia (Box OV)